<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QuickLoans</string>
    <string name="bullet">•</string>
    <string name="terms">Kindly note that &#8358;100 will be deducted from your card.
    We won\'t debit you if your loan request fails</string>

    <string name="agreement">Please read these Terms and Conditions carefully before using this service with your mobile device or any other means because by using
        this service you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions stated herein.

If you do not agree with this Terms and Conditions, please do not apply for this Service.

HOW TO USE THE QUICKLOANS.ng GOAL LENDING SERVICE

This Service is available to any Customer with an active Nigerian Bank account.

DEFINITIONS
In this agreement, the terms “You”, “Your”, “Customer” and “Borrower” shall mean the person who has applied for a credit facility
        and has agreed to the terms of this Agreement while “We”, “Us” “Our” and “Lender” shall mean Quickloans.ng
Account – means the Borrower’s existing Bank account.
Disbursement Date – means the date the Lender actually advanced the loan to the Borrower.
Payment Due Date – means loan repayment date subject to the total tenure of active loans
Loan – Money disbursed to Borrower.
Default – means any failure to meet your financial obligation due to us as at when due as we have independently determined and
        communicated to you as a result of this service.

Service – means the Quickloans,ng Lending Service for Customers provided by us/partners and comprises of the following services
Request a Loan
Receive a Loan
Pay a Loan
Use – means your accessing or using this service whether by your mobile device or by any other means made available by the service.
INTEREST/FEES
The Interest rate to be charged for this service shall be 15%-20% per 14days/Months/annum.
The interest rate may be increased or decreased from time to time by us. Such change in the interest rate will take effect following a
        minimum of ten (10) Business days written notice to you by email.
The above interest rate shall remain applicable in the event of you liquidating the loan before expiration.
The above rate does not preclude us from charging default fees and in the event of any dispute arising from these Terms and Conditions – cost
        of Litigation/Solicitors fees.
BORROWERS OBLIGATIONS
To ensure that you have an existing Bank account with a Nigerian financial institution.
To pay the loan sum including interest rate and other fees due to us. You promise to pay these rates/fees as agreed in this Agreement.
To use this service for your personal purpose only.
We reserve the right to presume that you have authorized any loan application made in your name using your account. You will be deemed
        responsible for any unauthorized application using your account/BVN unless you notify us, in writing of an imminent fraud by
        another person on your account within twenty-four (24) hours of such fraud.
We reserve the right to accept repayment provided you have given us adequate notice and repay fully the loan amount along with the accrued interest rate.
To fund account adequately to meet loan repayment obligation as at when due.

To honour all promises that I make in this Agreement.
To pay all interest/fees as provided in terms and conditions.

To promptly notify you if i change my name, mailing address, my email address or my telephone number


LENDERS OBLIGATIONS
To make the credit facility available to you subject to meeting the financial credibility criteria for the  amount requested.
To demand repayment from you as and when due.
To use all reasonable and legitimate means to collect the amount extended to you including all other fees.

EVENT OF DEFAULT
Default in terms of this Agreement will occur if:


You fail to make any scheduled repayment in full on or before the payment due date in accordance with the repayment plan given to you by us;
Any representation/information, warranty or assurance made or given by you in connection with the application for this loan or any information
        or documentation supplied by you is later discovered to be materially incorrect; or
You do anything which may prejudice our right in terms of this Agreement or causes us to suffer any loss or damage.
In the event of any default by you, we reserve the right to set off the outstanding loan obligation and other fees/rates from the Bank.

TERMINATION OF THIS LENDING ARRANGEMENT
In addition to termination by default, we may terminate this agreement at any time and for any reason subject to the requirements of applicable law.
Termination may occur when interest accrued on loan and principal is about to exceed 125% of total goal amount. Where this happens, the goal
        account will be liquidated to set off the loan.
Where Termination arises as a result of default, you will not be able to apply for this service again.


INDEMNIFICATION
We are exempted from any form of liability whatsoever for complying with any or all instruction(s) given by means of your credentials and accordingly,
        we shall not be responsible for any fraudulent, duplicate or erroneous instructions.
We are exempted from any liability for loss that may arise as a result of acts of hackers and other unauthorized access to your Account via this Service.
You agree to indemnify us for any failure to perform, or delay in performance of, any of our obligations under this Agreement that is caused by any
        act or event beyond our reasonable control or caused by you not fulfilling your obligations.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES
You expressly agree that your use of this service is at your sole risk. Neither the Lender nor any of its affiliates, or their respective directors,
        officers, employees, agents, contractors, affiliates, licencors warrants that this Service will shall be 100% perfect at all times. This
        service is provided on an “as is,” “as available” basis, without warranties of any kind, either express or implied, including, without
        limitation, those of merchantability and fitness for purpose.


LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
Under no circumstances shall we, our subsidiary and parent companies, or affiliates, or their respective directors, officers, employees, agents,
        contractors, or licensors, be liable for any direct or incidental, special or consequential damages under or arising from this agreement,
        whether for breach of contract, tortuous behaviour, negligence, or under any other cause of action, including without limitation, any
        liability for damages caused or allegedly caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, electrical surge/damage/interference,
        deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communications line failure, breakdown of equipment, software error,
        infringement, unauthorized access to, or theft, destruction, alteration, or use of, records.


GENERAL
This Agreement represents the entire understanding between us and your goodself with respect to the provision of this service.

Any amendment to this Agreement shall be made by us from time to time and communicated to you in writing.

You agree and undertake that for the period of this Agreement, you will continue to maintain a good credit score.

This Agreement shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the Federal Republic of Nigeria and, in the event of a dispute, same
        shall be subject to Arbitration in accordance with the provisions of the Arbitration and Conciliation Act, Cap A18 Laws of the Federation
        of Nigeria 2004. The Arbitration shall be held in English Language. The Arbitration shall be held in Lagos and the arbitral award shall be final.

We reserve the right to transfer or assign our rights and obligations under this Agreement (including its obligation to lend money to the Borrower
        or the amount owed under this Agreement) to another person. The Lender will only inform the Borrower if such a transfer causes the arrangements
        for the administration of this Agreement to change.

The Borrower authorizes and consents to all lawful access, use or disclosure of the Borrower’s particulars, data and information in the application by
        the Lender which may include but shall not be limited to purposes necessary to promote or sustain the business of the Lender; and the Borrower
        waives any claims the Borrower may have against the Lender arising from any such access, use or disclosure.</string>

    <string-array name="bank_codes">
        <item>00</item>
        <item>044</item>
        <item>023</item>
        <item>063</item>
        <item>050</item>
        <item>084</item>
        <item>070</item>
        <item>011</item>
        <item>214</item>
        <item>058</item>
        <item>030</item>
        <item>082</item>
        <item>014</item>
        <item>076</item>
        <item>221</item>
        <item>068</item>
        <item>232</item>
        <item>032</item>
        <item>033</item>
        <item>215</item>
        <item>035</item>
        <item>057</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gender">
        <item>Gender</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="employment">
        <item>Employment status</item>
        <item>Unemployed</item>
        <item>Self employed</item>
        <item>Employed</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="residential">
        <item>Residential status</item>
        <item>Owned</item>
        <item>Staying with someone</item>
        <item>Rented</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="state">
        <item>State</item>
        <item>Abia</item>
        <item>Adamawa</item>
        <item>Akwa Ibom</item>
        <item>Anambra</item>
        <item>Bauchi</item>
        <item>Bayelsa</item>
        <item>Benue</item>
        <item>Borno</item>
        <item>Cross River</item>
        <item>Delta</item>
        <item>Ebonyi</item>
        <item>Edo</item>
        <item>Ekiti</item>
        <item>Enugu</item>
        <item>FCT</item>
        <item>Gombe</item>
        <item>Imo</item>
        <item>Jigawa</item>
        <item>Kaduna</item>
        <item>Kano</item>
        <item>Katsina</item>
        <item>Kebbi</item>
        <item>Kogi</item>
        <item>Kwara</item>
        <item>Lagos</item>
        <item>Nassarawa</item>
        <item>Niger</item>
        <item>Ogun</item>
        <item>Ondo</item>
        <item>Osun</item>
        <item>Oyo</item>
        <item>Plateau</item>
        <item>Rivers</item>
        <item>Sokoto</item>
        <item>Taraba</item>
        <item>Yobe</item>
        <item>Zamfara</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="qualification">
        <item>Highest Qualification</item>
        <item>Primary school leaving certificate</item>
        <item>SSCE</item>
        <item>Undergraduate</item>
        <item>First Degree</item>
        <item>Masters</item>
        <item>PhD</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="bank_names">
        <item>Select Bank</item>
        <item>Access Bank</item>
        <item>CitiBank</item>
        <item>Diamond Bank</item>
        <item>EcoBank</item>
        <item>Enterprise Bank</item>
        <item>Fidelity Bank</item>
        <item>First Bank</item>
        <item>FCMB</item>
        <item>GTBank</item>
        <item>Heritage Bank</item>
        <item>KeyStone Bank</item>
        <item>MainStreet Bank</item>
        <item>Polaris Bank</item>
        <item>Stanbic IBTC Bank</item>
        <item>Standard Chartered Bank</item>
        <item>Sterling Bank</item>
        <item>Union Bank</item>
        <item>UBA Bank</item>
        <item>Unity Bank</item>
        <item>Wema Bank</item>
        <item>Zenith Bank</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
